univerteam.com 2015-05-28

# Univerteam Limited -

Univerteam Limited - Privacy Policy – 15th September, 2014
Univerteam Limited - #604, Tower A, New Trade Plaza 6 - On Ping Street, Shatin, N.T.
Hong Kong, (hereinafter referred to as “UNIVERTEAM”, "Company" or "We") respect
your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this
policy.
This policy and any other documents referred to in it describes the personal
information that we collect from you, or that you provide on this website
www.univerteam.com           (which may link to other Univerteam websites,
www.univercommerce.com,               www.univerwebs.com,          www.univerads.com,
www.univerapp.com) and how that information may be used or disclosed by us.
This Privacy Policy relates to all information we collect between you and this Website
and us.
All Univerteam websites contain privacy policies, which are equal to this Privacy
Policy.
Please read the following carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding
your personal information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our
policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By using or accessing our
Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time
and your continued use of the Website is deemed to be acceptance of such changes,
so please check the policy periodically for updates.
Children Under the Age of 18
Our Website is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age 18
may provide any personal information to or on the Website.
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are
under 18, please do not register on the Website, make any purchases through the
Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address,
telephone number or email address. In the event that we learn that we have
collected personal information from a child under age 18 without verification of
parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe that we might have
any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at
admin@univerteam.com.

COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
The Univerteam site may be viewed without having to reveal any personal
information. However, there are areas – such as effecting registration – that require
that information is shared, thus being necessary that future affiliates provide their
personal data.
The user’s identification data collection will be done by filling in an online registration
form and this will be done in accordance with the strictest security rules.
By registering in the Univerteam site the user provides personal information
necessary for the registration, such as, name, address, email address, telephone, etc.
The information collected is entered into the computer system, where it is treated
and automatically processed in the terms approved by the National Data Protection
Commission (CNPD). The information is intended for Univerteam service
management and interaction with the affiliates.
Univerteam guarantees the registered affiliate the possibility to access his personal
information through his/her “back office” and to review and correct information.
Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies
• Usage Details and IP Addresses. As you navigate through the Website, we may also
collect details of your visits to our Website, including, but not limited to, traffic data,
location data, logs and other communication data, whether this is required for our
own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access, as well as
information about your computer and Internet connection, including your IP address,
operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report
aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users'
equipment, browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
• Cookies. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general
Internet usage by using cookies. A cookie is a small file stored on the hard drive of
your computer. Use of cookies help us to improve our Website and to deliver a better
and more personalized service by enabling us to:

   • Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
   • Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our
       Website according to your individual interests.
   • Speed up your searches.
   • Recognize you when you return to our Website.
Cookies are generally safe, as they only identify your computer. Accepting a cookie
does not provide access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information
about you, other than the information you may choose to share. Other servers
cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate
browser settings. You can usually adjust browser settings to notify you of cookie
placement, decline certain cookies, or block cookies completely.
Uses Made of the Information
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any
personal information, in the following ways:
    • To present our Website and its contents in a suitable and effective manner for
    you and for your computer.
    • To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
    • To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts
    entered into between you and us.
    • To notify you about changes to our service.
    • To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you
    choose to do so.
    • In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide
to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over
your information:
• Cookies. If you do not wish us to collect cookies, you may set your browser to
refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note
that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
• Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your email
address used for promotional purposes by the Company, you can opt-out by sending
an email with the subject line “unsubscribe” to admin@univerteam.com. You can also
always opt-out of receiving email information from us other than the email informing
you of the completion of user registration, correction of user data, change of
password or change of applicable terms and conditions by sending us an email stating
your request at admin@univerteam.com. If we have sent you a promotional email,
you may send us an email at admin@univerteam.com asking to be omitted from
future email distributions. This opt-out does not apply to information provided to the
Company as a result of a product or service purchase, product service experience or
other transactions.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this document.
The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.
Contact Information
To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices,
contact us at admin@univerteam.com.
